A Finding Aid to the Dorothy Weiss Gallery Records, circa 1964-2001 (bulk 1984-2000), in the Archives of American Art AAA.doroweig
Archives of American Art
- Artist Files, circa 1964-2001; Series 1; 17.5 Linear feet Boxes 1-18, OV 21
  - Cohen, Carol, 1988-1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Corcoran, Annette (Box 3)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1984-1999 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Biographies and Résumés, 1990-1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Collector Records, 1990-2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Corcoran Catalog, 1994-1997 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1984-2000 (Box 3, Folder 8-11)
    - Loan Records, 1990-1998 (Box 3, Folder 12-13)
    - Price Lists, 1991-1999 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Printed Material, 1982-2000 (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
    - Photographs of Corcoran, circa 1990s (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 3, Folder 18-21)
  - Philip Cornelius (Box 3)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1982-1999 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1999 (Box 3, Folder 23-24)
    - Printed Material, 1976-1999 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 3, Folder 26-28)
  - Corney, Michael, General, circa 1993-1998 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Cox, Kris (Box 3)
    - General, 1984-1996 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Czeresko, Deborah, General, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Dam, Wouter (Box 3)
    - Correspondence, circa 1995-1999 (Box 3, Folder 33-34)
    - Printed Material, circa 1995-1999 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - da Silva, Marilyn, General, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Daunell, David, General, circa 1990s (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Daw, Deidre, General, circa 1992-2000 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - de la Torre, Einar and Jamex, General, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Delisle, Roseline (Box 4)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Photographic Material, 1980s (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Printed Material, 1983-1988 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Deller, Harris, General, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - de Swart, Peter (Box 4)
    - General, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Dickey, Kim, General, 1988-1999 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Dillingham, James Richard, General, 1981-1986 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Di Pasqua, Paul, General, 1990-1994 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - di Rosa, Veronica, General, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Donoghue, John, General, 1980-1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - D'Onofrio, Bernard, General, 1989-1994 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Duckworth, Ruth (Box 4)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, 1989-1994 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Biographies, Résumés, 1994, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Collector Records, 1989-2000 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Consignment Records, 1994-1997 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1987-2000 (Box 4, Folder 23-25)
    - Inventory and Price Lists, 1989-1998 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Printed Material, 1988-1993 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Shipping Records, 1989-1994 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Photograph of Duckworth, circa 1990 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1988-1994 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Earl, Jack (Box 4)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1990-1996 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Collector Records, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Consignment Records (other galleries), 1990-1994 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1997 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Price Lists, 1989-1997 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Printed Material, 1978-1993 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Shipping Records, 1991-1996 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Writings, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 4, Folder 39-41)
  - Eastman, Ken, General, 1990-2000 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Einfalt, Linda (Box 5)
    - General, 1984-1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1984-1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Ennis, Elizabeth, General, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Engel, Mary, General, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Ernst, Hedi-Katharina, General, 1995-1999 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Erteman, Kathy, General, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Eslick, Susan, General, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Fang, Marvin Minto, General, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Federighi, Christine, General, 1978-1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Feldman, Bella Tabak, General, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Fenci, Piero, General, 1978-1984 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Fenicchia, Concetta, General, 1983-1992 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Fisar, Marek, General, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Fleming, Carol, General, 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Fletcher, Sean A., General, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Fogarty, Jim, General, 1983-1991 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Frey, Barbara L., General, circa 1990-1994, undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Fritz, Donald C., General, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Fukazawa, Keiko, General, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Furman, David, General, 1990-1998 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    Includes photograph of Furman.
  - Gill, John (Box 5)
    - General, circa 1986-1994 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1986-1994 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Goodwin-Guerrero, Erin, General, 1986-1992 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Grebe, Robin, General, 1991-2001 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Griffith, Laura, General, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Griffith, Robert (Box 5)
    - General, 1993-1997 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1993-1997 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Grimm, Jane B., General, circa 1994-1997 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Gronborg, Erik, General, circa 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Gudjonsdottir, Kristin, General, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Haas, Amanda, General, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Hafner, Dorothy, General, circa 1983-1991 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Hashimoto, Barbara, General, 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Heid, Thomas, General, 1982-1987 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Heikoop, Govert, General, 1992-1998 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Hepburn, Tony (Box 6)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1986-1992 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1997 (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
    - Printed Material, 1978-1994 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      Oversized poster housed in OV 21.
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Hilferty, Patrick, General, 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Hobson, Charles (Box 6)
    - General, 1993-1997 (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1993-1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Hoch, Deborah, General, 1988-1992 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Holcomb, Jan, General, 1978, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Honda, Shingo, General, 1988-1999 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Hope, Linda, General, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Hovig-Schiltz, Kate, General, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Howard, Susan, General, circa 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Hude, Katrina, Consignment Records, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Huff, Jason, General, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Hughto, Margie, General, 1980-1991 (Box 6, Folder 20-21)
    Includes piece of handmade paper signed by Hughto.
  - Hunt, William, General, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Includes slide transparency, possibly of Hunt; oversized material housed in OV 21.
  - Hunter, Justin, General, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Hydman-Vallien, Ulrica, General, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Ikeda, Yoshiro, General, 1984, 1991-1994 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Irwin, Jeff (Box 6)
    - General, 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1995-1999 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Isupov, Sergei, General, 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Iwata, Kiyomi, General, 1992-1999 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Includes samples of Auric Grid Hanging and Auric Grid Hanging Two; oversized material housed in OV 21.
  - Jacques, Frank, General, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Jameson, Philip, General, 1983-1988 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Jeck, Doug (Box 6)
    - General, 1990-1999 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1995-1999 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Jones, Cassandra, General, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Joseph, Bo, General, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Joyce, Tim, General, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Kahl, Fred, General, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Kaneko, Jun (Box 7)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1988-1998 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Biographies, Résumés, circa 1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Collector Records, 1990-2000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Consignment Records, 1990-1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Contract, Bemis Center for Contemporary Art, 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1986-2000 (Box 7, Folder 6-8)
    - Inventory and Price Lists, circa 1986-1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Invoices, 1990-1996 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Loan Forms, 1989, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Printed Material, 1983-1999 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Photographs of Kaneko, circa 1986-1990s (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1988-1999 (Box 7, Folder 14-16)
  - Kaplan, Alissa, General, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Karina, Elena, General, 1982-1995 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Kehlmann, Robert (Box 7)
    - General, 1978-1996 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Oversized material housed in OV 21.
    - Photographic Material, circa 1992 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Kendall, Gail, General, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Kerrigan, Thomas, General, circa 1983-1999 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - King, David, General, circa 1988-1999 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Kirillova, Julia, General, 1996-1999 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Koblitz, Karen (Box 7)
    - General, 1977-1988 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Inventory Records, 1977-1982 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Kohl, Joyce and Gayle Luchessa, General, 1978-1983 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Kovatch, Ron, General, 1987-1991 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Krasnican, Susie, General, circa 1988-1991 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Krusoe, Sana (Box 7)
    - General, 1980-1993, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980-1993 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Kuraoka, David, General, circa 1980 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Kvapil, Jay, Announcement, DW Gallery, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - LaBianca, Lawrence (Box 7)
    - General, 1994-1999 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1994-1999 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Laemmle, Cheryl, General, 1991-1997 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Laky, Gyöngy, General, 1980-1984 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Lancet, Marc, General, 1992-1999 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Larocque, Jean-Pierre, General, 1995-1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - La Scola, Judith, General, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Lastomirsky, Geo, General, 1993-1999 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Lawrence, Les, General, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Leedy, Jim, General, 1987, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Levi, David and Dimitri Michaelides, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Levin-Lau, Katherine, General, 1985-1992 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Lieberman, Walter, General, 1994-1998 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Lindquist, Mark, General, 1993, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Lipofsky, Marvin, General, 1975-2000 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Low-Beer, Susan, General, circa 1991-1993 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Lucero, Michael (Box 8)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1991-1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Biographies, Résumés, 1990, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Collector Records, 1991-1999 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Consignment Records, 1991-1998 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1999 (Box 8, Folder 17-18)
    - Loan Forms, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Price Lists, circa 1991-1999 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Printed Material, 1983-2000 (Box 8, Folder 21-23)
    - Re-sale Records, 1994-1996 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 8, Folder 25-28)
  - Lynch, Nathan, General, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Mace, Flora and Joey Kirkpatrick, General, 1986-1994 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Magel, Catherine, General, 1984-1996 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Makins, James (Box 8)
    - General, 1992-1997 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1992-1997 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Mangus, Kirk, General, 1983-1989, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Marak, Louis (Box 8)
    - General, 1982-1999 (Box 8, Folder 35-36)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1982-1999 (Box 8, Folder 37-39)
  - Marioni, Paul, General, 1987, 1997-1999 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Massaro, Karen, General, 1995-2000 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Marquis, Richard (Box 9)
    See also Bartneck, Lea.
    - Correspondence, 1979-1998 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Printed Material, 1981-1998 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1979-1998 (Box 9, Folder 4-5)
  - Mathieu, Paul (Box 9)
    - General, 1985-1994 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Photographic Material, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Matthews, Kazuko Kayasuga (Box 9)
    - General, 1985-1996 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Photograph of Matthews, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
      One slide transparency.
  - Matuszewski, Gloria, General, 1994-1998 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Mayeri, Beverly (Box 9)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1990-2000 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Collector Records, 1990-2000 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Consignment Records, 1991-1996 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1999 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Loan Form, circa 1992 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Price Lists, 1990-1996 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Printed Material, 1981-2000 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Re-sale Records, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 9, Folder 19-20)
  - McBride, Kathryn, General, 1984-1999 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - McDonnell, Mark, General, 1983-1993 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Meiners, Dennis, General, 1994-1998 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Melchert, Jim, General, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Messenger, Mark, General, circa 1992-1999 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Miller, Bradley, General, 1993-1999 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Mills, Rick, General, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Milnes, Robert, General, 1990-1998 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Miyata, Masako, General, 1990-1998 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Mizuno, Keisuke, General, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Montgomery, Steven, General, 1996-2000 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Moquin, Richard, General, circa 1981 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Moran, Mike, General, 1995-1998 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Morris, James (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1997 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Printed Material, 1985-1993 (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1985-1997 (Box 10, Folder 3-4)
  - Morris, William (Box 10)
    - Collector Records, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Consignment Records, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1998 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Printed Material, 1983-1999 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Re-sale Records, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1993-1999 (Box 10, Folder 10-12)
  - Mosman, Timothy (Box 10)
    - General, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Photographs of Mosman, circa 1980s (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Musler, Jay (Box 10)
    - Collector Records, 1984-1996 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Consignment Records, 1991-1995 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1998 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Inactive Inventory, 1980-1992 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Invoices, 1981-1997 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Loan Forms, 1994-1997 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Price Lists, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Printed Material, 1981-1998 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Photographs of Musler, 1982, circa 1995 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 10, Folder 25-26)
  - Myers, Kevin, General, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Nakata, Rory, General, 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Natzler, Otto and Gertrud, General, 1971-1993 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Nelson, Keiko, General, 1989-1996 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Notkin, Richard, General, circa 1984-2000 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - O'Connor, Casey, General, circa 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Olivier, Diane (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1992 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Printed Material, 1985-1991 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1985-1992 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Patti, Thomas, General, 1979-1986 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Pearson, Todd (Box 10)
    - General, 1986-1994 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1986-1994 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Peet, Anne, General, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Perkins, Flo, General, 1981-1990 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Perotto, Glen Rogers, General, 1986-1992 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Podmore, Amy (Box 11)
    - General, circa 1987-1989 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Includes 2 postcards illustrated by Podmore.
    - Photograph of Podmore, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1987-1990 (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
  - Popelka, Jeremy (Box 11)
    - General, 1991-1997 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1990-1997 (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
  - Powers, Pike, General, 1990-1998 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Price, Ken, General, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Quaglita, Narcissus, General, 1994-1998 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Quinn, Jeanne, General, 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Rainey, Clifford (Box 11)
    - Correspondence, 1992-1998 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Printed Material, 1987-1998 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Photograph of Rainey, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1987-1998 (Box 11, Folder 15-16)
  - Reinertson, Lisa (Box 11)
    - General, circa 1988-1991 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Photograph of Reinertson, circa 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      Photograph of the artist working on Martin Luther King, Jr., sculpture.
  - Reiss, Walter, General, 1995-1998 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Reitz, Donald (Box 11)
    - General, 1986-1990 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Photographs of Reitz, circa 1986-1990 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Rhodes, Daniel, General, circa 1964-1989 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Rice, Jacqueline, General, 1984-1992 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Riley, Cheryl Renee, General, circa 1988-1998 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Ritchey, Rik, General, 1990-1993 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Ritchie, Gail, General, 1985-1996 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Ritchie, Leah, General, 1991-1998 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Roberts, Amy, General, 1983-1985 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    Includes card with an original print.
  - Roberts, Gregory (Box 11)
    - Correspondence, 1991-2000 (Box 11, Folder 29-30)
    - Printed Material, 1993-1999 (Box 11, Folder 31-32)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1990s (Box 11, Folder 33-34)
  - Roberts, Nancy Rawls, General, 1992-1998 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Rock, Joellyn, Photographic Material, circa 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Rohlfing, John G., General, 1988-1999 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Rosdol, Leslie, General, 1992-1995 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Rosen, Annabeth (Box 12)
    - General, 1995-2001 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Printed Material, 1995-1999 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1994-2000 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Rosenberg, Edor, General, circa 1987-1997 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Roth, Leslie, Photographic Material, circa 1993-1995 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Rotschild, Jason, Photographic Material, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Ruffner, Ginny (Box 12)
    - General, 1984-1998 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Printed Material, 1985-1998 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Rush, Jerry, General, 1994-1998 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Sabrina, Amy, Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Sakway, Hap, General, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Saloman, Judith, General, circa 1988-1994 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Samios, William, General, 1992-1999 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Sanders, Terri Ann, General, 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Sasaki, Hitoshi, General, circa 1983-1987 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Savage, Juta (Box 12)
    - General, 1983-1990 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      Oversized illustrated letter of drawings for Teapot Invitational housed in OV 21.
    - Photographic Material, circa 1980-1990 (Box 12, Folder 20-21)
  - Scanga, Italo, General, 1992-1998 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Scheer, Elaine, General, 1985-1998 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Scheid, Anne, General, 1994-2000 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Scheiner, Michael, General, 1988-1991 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Schnabel, Jo Ann, General, 1988-1993 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Schwarz, June, General, 1969-1989 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Scotchie, Virginia (Box 12)
    - General, 1983-1996 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1983-1996 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Sedestrom, Robert, General (includes a handmade card), circa 1987-1993 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Shaffer, Mary, Printed Material, 1992-1998 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Shay, Robert, General, 1983-1995 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Sherrill, Michael, General, 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Shrosbree, James R., General, circa 1980-1996 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Silliman, Christopher (Box 12)
    - General, circa 1990-1998 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1989-1998 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Silver, Anna, General, circa 1984-1996 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Simon, Sandy, General, circa 1982-1998 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Slusky, Joe, General, 1985-1990 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Barbara Bell (Box 13)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1986-1991 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1994 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Printed Material, 1985-1991 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1985-1994 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Sperry, Robert (Box 13)
    - General, 1986-1999 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Printed Material, 1981-1993 (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
    - Photographs of Sperry, circa 1980s-1990s (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Stanbridge, Linda (Box 13)
    - General, 1993-1997 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1993-1997 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Statom, Therman (Box 13)
    - Active Inventories, 1992-1999 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1992-2000 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Biography, [1997] (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Collector Records, 1992-1999 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Consignment Records, 1992-1999 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1984, 1992-1999 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Price Lists, 1992-1997 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Printed Material, 1981-2000 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Photographs of Statom, circa 1995 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 23-24)
    - Photographic Material and Permissions, circa 1992-1994 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Stein, Livia, General, 1986-1989 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Stephenson, John, General, 1985-1990 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Stewart, William, 1995-1999 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Strasser, Dharma, 1997-1999 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Sugiyami, Michio, 1986-1992 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    Also Ceramic Art Park, Shiga, Japan.
  - Sullivan, Karen W., General, circa 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Swanson, Richard, General, 1995-1996 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Takayama-Ogawa, Joan, General, circa 1991-1999 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Tarantino, Claudia, General, 1987-1998 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Taylor, Yoshio (Box 13)
    - Announcements and Press Releases, DW Gallery, 1983-1994 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1993 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Printed Material, 1982-1997 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Photographs of Taylor, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1983-1987 (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
  - Tedesco, Photographic Material, circa 1998 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Temkin, Noam, General, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Terestman, Julie, General, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Thayer, Susan, General, circa 1992-1997 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Theiss, Vernon, General, circa 1988-1996 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Thompson, Cappy, General, circa 1996-1998 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Tomb, David, General, 1989-1997 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Tsang, Re-Cheng, General, circa 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Tsutsumi, Nobuko, General, 1994-1996 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Includes slides of Tsutsumi.
  - Turner, Robert (Box 14)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1997 (Box 14, Folder 13-14)